worldwidefred.com 2013-06-02

# Fred & Friends » Privacy Policy

_**What information do we collect?**_

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or Easy Aces Inc. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

_**What do we use your information for?**_

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

\- To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

\- To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

\- To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

_**How do we protect your information?**_

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to automatically process reorders.

_**Do we use cookies?**_

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

_**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**_

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. In addition, if we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred.

_**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**_

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all registered wholesale users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Account' page.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

_**Online Privacy Policy Only**_

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

_**Your Consent**_

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

_**Changes to our Privacy Policy**_

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on October 20, 2012

_**Contacting Us**_

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.fredandfriends.com  
30 Martin St  
Cumberland, RI 02864  
USA  
webmaster@fredandfriends.com
